<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[This is a Thing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Just pointing out stuff I think is cool and talking about it]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:52:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Gatsby]]></title><description><![CDATA[So, it makes sense to start this blog off by talking about the technology powering it. Everybody knows about react already, even outside the…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/gatsby/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/gatsby/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 04:31:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;So, it makes sense to start this blog off by talking about the technology powering it. Everybody knows about react already, even outside the web world, but Gatsby was new to me, and I think it’s really cool. Basically, you build a mostly standard react-based site, run it through gatsby, and it spits out a static website for you. I haven’t figured out everything it can do yet, and I’m no great shakes at react yet anyway, but I’ve been super happy with it. It’s really fast, and makes a lot of things really easy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check it out at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gatsbyjs.org/&quot; title=&quot;https://www.gatsbyjs.org/&quot;&gt;https://www.gatsbyjs.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/media/gatsby-website.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[First!]]></title><description><![CDATA[When I was at my first job, I’d often see something cool and post a link to slack saying “this is a thing”. I figured that people would see…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/first-post/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/first-post/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 04:31:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;When I was at my first job, I’d often see something cool and post a link to slack saying “this is a thing”. I figured that people would see whatever it is and, if it was relevant to them, they’d probably know pretty quickly why I’d pointed it out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway, that’s what this blog is about. Hopefully you get something out of it.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>